myclassboard.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy policy - School Management Software, MyClassboard erp

MyClassboard Educational Solutions pvt ltd ("MyClassboard") respects the privacy of people who use the [www.myclassboard.com](http://www.myclassboard.com/) website or other MyClassboard services. This privacy statement ("policy") reflects the current information practices of MyClassboard. Should there be any future changes to our privacy policy, we will continue to post them on this page.

In this policy, "you" or "your" refers to any person or entity subscribing to and/or using the Service ("Users"). Unless otherwise stated, "MyClassboard," "we," or "our" will refer collectively to MyClassboard Educational Solutions pvt ltd

#### Collection of Data

Anonymous Information: For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes anonymous data that is not linked to your personal data, such as your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring website addresses.  
Personally Identifying Information: When you register as a member or request information, we will use our registration and online enrollment forms to collect personally identifying information, such as your full name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, educational background, and credit card information ("personal data"). In addition, if you contact us via an e-mail or offline, we may collect the personal data that you voluntarily provide us at that time. You can visit most of the public pages on our website site without giving us any personal data.

#### Use of Data

The information we collect is used for the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal data, to improve the content of our web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual user, used to notify users about updates to our website, shared with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations, used by us to contact users for marketing purposes, used by us to contact users for employment opportunities, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the Website.  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or in regards to technical or billing or product related issues when deemed necessary during our regular office hours.

#### Review and Correction

Upon request, we offer users the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, and transaction information. Users can have this information corrected by sending an e-mail or writing to us at the address below or by updating their profile by logging on through their account at [www.myclassboard.com](http://www.myclassboard.com/)

#### Maintaining Privacy 

As stated above, MyClassboard will maintain the confidentiality of all user communications, which contains personal information transmitted directly to MyClassboard. Postings by a user on any public arena, such as a message board or in any chat room, will not and cannot be protected as confidential.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or suggestions on how to improve our privacy to all users, please contact us at:  
MyClassboard Educational Solutions pvt ltd  
Cyber View Towers, Vittal Rao Nagar,  
Behind image Hospitals, Madhapur,  
Hyderabad-500081, India. Phone: +91-9246477770  
+9140 - 65557770, +9140 - 64518880  
Email: support@myclassboard.com
